<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TinyGods.Dev</title>
    <link>https://tinygods.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TinyGods.Dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tinygods.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Emigrant Lives Telegram Bot</title>
      <link>https://tinygods.dev/posts/emigrant-lives-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tinygods.dev/posts/emigrant-lives-bot/</guid>
      <description>A demo bot that provides insights on cities with large Russian expat communities. Perfect for potential movers or the curious!
Emigrant Lives Bot
The bot employs TinyGods&#39; data processing pipeline, fetching and aggregating information from multiple sources including public APIs and websites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Телегам-бот Emigrant Lives</title>
      <link>https://tinygods.dev/ru/posts/emigrant-lives-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tinygods.dev/ru/posts/emigrant-lives-bot/</guid>
      <description>Демонстрационный бот, который предоставляет информацию о городах с большими русскоязычными общинами. Идеально подходит для потенциальных переселенцев или просто любопытных!
Emigrant Lives Bot
Бот использует платформу обработки данных TinyGods, получая и агрегируя информацию из множества источников, включая публичные API и веб-сайты.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Price Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://tinygods.dev/price-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tinygods.dev/price-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>We automate the collection and analysis of competitor prices for you. Focus on developing your online store while we keep our finger on the pulse and monitor the market.
What Can We Do for You? Get a report with a complete analysis of prices in online stores. You will have access to the following indicators:
 Competitor prices for similar products Average market price Median price among sellers Minimum and maximum market price Difference between your price and the average, median, and minimum prices in percentage Recommended price  With a large dataset, it is possible to calculate seasonal dynamics and predict market fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programmers are tiny gods</title>
      <link>https://tinygods.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tinygods.dev/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programmers are tiny gods</title>
      <link>https://tinygods.dev/ru/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tinygods.dev/ru/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telegram Bots</title>
      <link>https://tinygods.dev/telegram-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tinygods.dev/telegram-bot/</guid>
      <description>Get started today. Let&amp;#39;s talk about a project, collaboration or an idea you may have  Let&#39;s work together to streamline your data processes and unlock new opportunities.  Contact us at tinygodsdev@gmail.com or use the form.      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Мониторинг цен</title>
      <link>https://tinygods.dev/ru/price-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tinygods.dev/ru/price-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>Автоматизируем для вас сбор и анализ цен конкурентов. Сосредоточьтесь на развитии своего онлайн-магазина, пока мы будем держать руку на пульсе и мониторить рынок.
Что мы можем для вас сделать? Получите отчет с полным анализом цен на рынке онлайн-магазинов. Вам будут доступны следующие показатели:
 цены конкурентов на аналогичные товары средняя цена на рынке медианная цена среди продавцов минимальная и максимальная цена на рынке отличие вашей цены от средней, медианной и минимальной в процентах рекомендованная цена  На большом наборе данных есть возможность рассчитать сезонную динамику и предсказать колебания рынка.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Телеграм-боты</title>
      <link>https://tinygods.dev/ru/telegram-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tinygods.dev/ru/telegram-bot/</guid>
      <description> Начните уже сегодня. Обсудим проект, сотрудничество или идею, которая у вас есть  Давайте вместе оптимизируем ваши процессы работы с данными и откроем новые возможности.  Свяжитесь с нами по адресу tinygodsdev@gmail.com или используйте форму.      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
